nymgo.com 2018-08-23

# NYMGO

## Nymgo privacy policy

Nymgo is committed to respecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal data, traffic data and communications content. 

###  1\. Information collected 

Nymgo may gather and use information about you, including (but not limited to) information in the following categories: 

  * (a) Identification data (e.g. name, address, telephone number, mobile number, email address, country of residence); 
  * (b) Electronic identification data (e.g. IP addresses, cookies); 
  * (c) Survey results; 
  * (d) Information about your usage of and interaction with the Nymgo software, our products and websites including computer, platform, device and connection information, device capability, bandwidth, statistics on page views, and traffic to and from our websites, browser type; 
  * (e) Products or services ordered and delivered; 
  * (f) List of your contacts; 
  * (g) Correspondence between you and Nymgo; 
  * (h) Traffic data (data processed for the purpose of the conveyance of communications or the billing thereof, including, but not limited to, the duration of the call, the number calling and the number called); and 
  * (i) Mobile device information, such as manufacturer's name, device model number, operating system, carrier network; 

###  2\. Use of personal information 

  * take, process or deliver orders made via our websites, invoice you or notify you of the status of your order; 
  * provide other services for you (as described when we collect the information); 
  * provide you with customer support and troubleshoot problems; 
  * compare information for accuracy; 
  * inform you about service updates and faults; 
  * request feedback or participation in on-line surveys; 
  * resolve disputes; 
  * verify your identity; 
  * customize, measure, and improve the Nymgo software, our products and websites; 
  * organize and carry out Nymgo's marketing or promotional operations/offers, contests, games and similar events; and 
  * protect your and Nymgo's interests, including in particular to enforce our Terms of Service and prevent and fight against fraud, (together, the Purposes). 

###  3\. Disclosure of personal information 

  * Except as provided below, Nymgo will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise transfer any personal and/or traffic data or communications content without your explicit permission, unless it is obliged to do so under applicable laws or by order of the competent authorities. 
  * Nymgo may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, to protect Nymgo's interests, fight against fraud and to enforce our policies or to protect anyone's rights, property, or safety 

###  4\. Nymgo Cookies 

  * By using Nymgo's websites and/or software you are giving your consent to the use of cookies. You can choose to reject cookies at any time, either by changing your browser settings (if your browser permits) or by ceasing to use Nymgo's websites and/or software or by using the applicable opt-out functions. You should be aware that certain features are only available through the use of cookies and if you choose not to accept cookies, such features may not be available to you. 
  * Nymgo uses the following analytics partners to track volume of usage on the sites and to help improve the features and layout of its websites: 
  * Google Analytics is an analytics tool that gathers anonymous statistical information such as the number of times you have been to Nymgo's website, the time and date of your last visit, the search engine and keyword that you used to find our site, the link that you accessed our site from and the location from which you accessed our site. It does not track your journeys across other websites. 
  * To opt out of Google Analytics cookies, please visit: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout 

###  5\. Your Profile 

  * Your user profile is the information provided by you at registration which is displayed in your Nymgo profile in the Nymgo software client and on your personal details page in your account on [_www.nymgo.com_](http://www.nymgo.com/) It may include your Nymgo username, full name, address, telephone and mobile numbers, country, language. You can access your user profile from the "Nymgo" mobile app, software client or from your account on [_www.nymgo.com_](http://www.nymgo.com/) in order to view, correct or complete information, remove non-mandatory information. 

###  6\. Third Parties 

  * Nymgo websites may contain links that will let you leave Nymgo 's website and access another website. Linked websites are not under the control of Nymgo and these websites have different privacy policies. The Nymgo Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information that is acquired on the websites or through your use of the Nymgo software, Nymgo products and/or your relationship with Nymgo, so Nymgo urges you to be careful when you enter any personal information online. Nymgo accepts no responsibility or liability for these other websites. 
  * If you use any extras, plug-ins or third party applications together with the Nymgo software ("Applications"), the provider of such Applications may obtain access to certain personal information about you. Nymgo does not and cannot control how the provider of Applications may use any personal information connected in connection with such Applications. Please ensure that you review any privacy policies or other terms applicable to the use of such Application before installation. 

###  7\. Protection of personal data 

  * Nymgo will take appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect the personal data and traffic data provided to it or collected by it with due observance of the applicable obligations and exceptions under the relevant legislation. 

###  8\. Contacting you 

  * Nymgo may from time to time ask you to provide information on your experiences which will be used to measure and improve quality. You are at no time under any obligation to provide any of such data. Any and all information which is voluntarily submitted in feedback forms on the website or any survey that you take part in is used for the purposes of reviewing this feedback and improving the Nymgo software, Nymgo products and websites. 
  * Nymgo may contact you to send you messages about faults and service issues. Further, Nymgo reserves the right to use email, the Nymgo software or SMS to notify you of any eventual claims related to your use of Nymgo software, the Nymgo websites and/or Nymgo products, including without limitation claims of violation of third party rights. 
  * Nymgo may also use email, SMS or the Nymgo software to keep you up to date with news about the Nymgo software and Nymgo products that you have purchased and/or to inform you about other Nymgo products or other Nymgo related information. You can opt-out of the receipt of alerts and/or promotional emails by clicking the "unsubscribe" link on the email that you receive. 

###  9\. How to update personal data? 

  * You have the right to access and, where relevant, to amend your personal information. Some of your information may be viewed or edited online by signing into your account page on [_www.nymgo.com._](http://www.nymgo.com/) We will respond to requests to view, correct, complete or remove your personal information within a reasonable period of time and upon verification of your identity. 
  * Nymgo will use all reasonable endeavors to accommodate requests to delete personal information unless it is required to be retained by law or for lawful business purposes. 

###  10\. Records of personal data 

  * Nymgo will retain your information for as long as is necessary to: (1) fulfil any of the Purposes or (2) comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent courts. 

###  11\. Privacy Policy updates 

  * Nymgo will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our software and/or products and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will update the "last revised" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy or in how we will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification. You agree that your continued use of the Nymgo software or Nymgo products after notice shall constitute your acceptance of the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Nymgo is collecting, using, and protecting your information. 

###  Splendor Telecom UK Limited 

  * Nymgo S.A.  
Suite 14, 3 Rue Thomas Edisson  
L-1445 Strassen  
Luxembourg

Registered in Luxembourg  
Registration Number: B 161 457  
VAT Number: LU24906139

Telephone: +44 (20) 33553209  
Fax: +352 24611970  
Email: [_info@nymgo.com_](mailto:info@nymgo.com)  
© NYMGO - Last revised: March 14 2012
